I want to put up a video talking a little
Quiero poner un vídeo hablando un poco
about the reactions that it has had on social networks
de las reacciones en redes que ha tenido
But before they put it up they are
Pero antes de que lo pongan te están
telling you in the chat that if you see
diciendo en el chat que si ves ahora
Rocío Carrasco now how she treats her, would you
Rocío Carrasco cómo la trata que si le
call her beautiful again and all
volverías a llamar guapísima y todas
that stuff, if not yes of course obviously
esas cosas sino sí claro evidentemente
but I don't understand the question like if
pero yo no entiendo la pregunta a ver si
a person is polite
una persona es educada contigo y O sea
to you and I mean you have to always be polite whether you like them or not more or less I agree on their things let's say I'm with Antonio David Flores and with his family on this issue but 100% Maybe I'll have another difference with Antonia Vi in other
diferencia con Antonia vi en otros
scenarios but I think that in all this
escenarios pero yo creo que en todo esto
at the moment I can't think
de momento no se me ocurre ahora mismo
of any scenario right now in which or rather in
en algún escenario en el que o sea en
some controversy like this one she has
alguna polémica de esta de las que tiene
with Rosarito in which I can't imagine
con Rosarito en las que no me imagino
that he wouldn't have been
que él tampoco habrá sido
a saint either and would have made his mistakes in
un santo y habría tenido sus errores en
life okay but
la vida vale pero
if I meet a person on the
yo sí a una persona me la encuentro por
street and I'm recording
la calle y voy grabando encima en
live on top of that, well no,
directo pues no
any question that occurs to me if I'm
alguna pregunta que se me ocurra si voy
prepared not like the other time no, when it
preparado no como la otra vez no que me
caught me by surprise that  don't
pilló como muy de sorpresa que no hay
forget that the last thing on my
que olvidar que lo último que se me
mind that night
pasaba a mí por la cabeza esa noche que
I was walking with my camera in hand was running into
iba yo con mi cámara en mano cruzarme
Rocio Carrasco at a roundabout you
con Rocío Carrasco una rotonda me
know what But yes, a fantasy, what a
entiende Pero que sí una fantasía qué
weekend it is Javi we went from a
fin de semana es Javi pasamos de una
fantasy not only not only the
fantasía no solamente no solamente el
meeting but then the next day
encuentro sino luego el día siguiente
too let's see What do you want me to tell you, I'm
también a ver yo Qué quieres que te diga
dying of laughter to run into Rocio
yo me descojono de encontrarme a Rocio
Carrasco and Rocio Carrasco telling me you
Carrasco y que Rocio Carrasco me diga tú
again here Well, look at my dress I don't know come on,
otra vez aquí Pues mira mi vestido No sé
goodbye gorgeous but Javier the
venga Adiós guapísima pero Javier lo
best, the best was that he told you about the
mejor lo mejor fue que te dijo lo de la
series about his parents and we never saw it
serie de sus padres y nunca lo vimos
coming
venir
Javier Oliveira
total Javier oliveira
gave me an exclusive and and it seemed to us that
me dio una exclusiva y y nos dio que
now when they give it to me You say no, I
ahora cuando me la dan a mí Dices no di
gave it to us like you say in plural, he gave us
nos dio como dices tú en plural nos dio
an exclusive, say it
una exclusiva
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
dilo no no no no no no no no no no no
because it wasn't live and he did it
porque no fue en directo y la hizo
because he loves me deep down because he
porque me quiere en el fondo porque le
likes me, whatever Of
gusto o sea
course She told me you're my
Claro Ella me dijo eres mi youtuber
favorite youtuber there are other youtubers that make me feel
favorito hay otros youtubers que me dan
sorry for and I love them
pena y me encanta
what did she tell me I love that from
qué es lo que me dijo Me encanta que de
time to time this is a joke  no
vez en cuando esto es una broma no es
joke just kidding just kidding Yeah yeah it was brutal
broma es broma es broma Sí sí fue brutal
eh How did that get away from us eh Yes the
eh Como se nos escapó eso eh Sí la
truth is that yes the truth is that we are in
verdad que sí la verdad que estamos en
La Parra many times we don't give it here we
la Parra muchas veces no la damos aquí
give it to ourselves that we are the best
de nos la damos de que somos el mejor
YouTube channel Marina we are in La
canal de YouTube Marina estamos en la
Parra many times and we are Well I don't
Parra muchas veces y lo somos Bueno no
know not to give us his exclusive garracuna and we don't realize and
sé no darnos su garracuna exclusiva y no
also he said and also he
nos damos cuenta y además dijo y además
said and I told you eh it's that
dijo y te lo he dicho a ti eh
on top of that he told me It's that on top of that he
es que encima me lo dijo Es que encima
told me and I'm telling you so you can see
me dijo y te lo digo a ti para que veas
well how you don't tell me because he
bien como que no me lo dices a mí porque
wants to give the news in the place where everyone is
quiere dar la noticia en el sitio donde
going to enter that by the way
se va a entrar a todo el mundo que por
today we are going to have another visit But in the
hoy vamos a tener otra visita Pero al
end well, we
final pues bueno
were going to have it again, he has already given it a
ya íbamos a tener otra vez ya la ha dado
cut but I don't rule out that it will be I don't
corte pero no descarto que sea no
rule out that it will be another day
descarto que sea otro día
I think that deep down You know I think that deep down
yo creo que en el fondo Sabes Yo creo
But well,
que en el fondo Pero bueno autoriza
Javier Oliveira authorizes me to control my
Javier oliveira para que controle mi
mind Well I don't know if I will have that, it's a lot of
mente Bueno no sé si tendré eso es mucha
responsibility eh that's a lot of
responsabilidad eh eso es mucha
responsibility let's watch the video that
responsabilidad vamos a ver el vídeo que
our Indian made before moving on to
ha hecho nuestro indio antes de pasar a
the next topics because  I wanted to
los siguientes temas porque quería
comment a little on people's reaction
comentar un poco la reacción de la gente
on social media Marina, which has been quite a lot.
en redes Marina que ha sido bastante
First of all, well, let's put up the
en primer lugar bueno vamos a poner el
video. Well, it's another use
vídeo bueno es otra es otra utilización
of the figure of children to
de la figura de los niños para
crush me and to make
para machacarme a mí y para y para ganar
money.
dinero
That's the good father.
ese es el buen padre
In this case, it would be living off your ex-wife.
en su caso sería vive de tu ex mujer
Until you can live off your children,
Hasta que puedas vivir de tus hijos
Rocío, until now, the pension that she's claiming.
Rocío hasta ahora pensión que reclama
Look, Carlota, on the 30th, I was
Mira Carlota yo el día 30
called to testify
se me llamó para declarar
and I considered it to be good. Today, my lawyer and I, given the
y yo consideré bueno Yo hoy y mi abogado
procedural irregularities and irregularities, such as the fact that I am
procesales y regularidades como que a mí
notified of
lo que se me notifica es se me notifica
the complaint here at home, but I am not
aquí en mi casa la querella pero no se
notified of anything else.
me notifica absolutamente nada más no se
My lawyer has not been notified of the day that
le ha traslado a mi abogado del día que
this person is going to testify on the
esta persona va a ir a declarar el día
23rd. That statement is made.
23 esa declaración se produce
In this case, it's mine. I am present, so
en este caso es el mío presente entonces
given the many irregularities.
ante un montón de irregularidades
We have been
Nosotros hemos ido
filing appeals. All the appeals have
presentando recursos todos los recursos
not yet been resolved. So,
aún no han sido resueltos Entonces yo a
what I told your honor is that
su señoría lo que lo que le dije Es que
at that time I was not going to testify,
yo en ese momento no iba a declarar
but I would be delighted to
pero que estaría encantadísima de
testify and to tell you what I have to
declarar y de contarle lo que tengo que
tell you, but once  that all those little
decirle pero una vez que todos esos esos
bumps those
bachecitos esas irregularidades
procedural irregularities were resolved the issue
procesales estuvieran resueltas el tema
of the child is unnecessary and it will be known by me and
del niño se sobra y se sabrá por mí y lo
I will tell it and I will prove it when and
contaré yo y lo demostraré yo cuándo y
where I don't know
dónde no lo sé
but I have to prove it just like I
pero que tengo que demostrarlo igual que
proved the case of the girl I will
demostré el caso de la niña lo
prove it because as with the
demostraré porque al igual que con el
other case there is
otro caso
another plot in the middle and there is a
hay otra trama en medio y hay una trama
very big plot behind that
muy gorda detrás de eso
well I have not proven it in the end also
pues no la demostrado al final también
the newspaper archives I had forgotten
la hemeroteca se me había olvidado a mí
this already clear Yes yes of course I mean will
esto ya claro Sí sí claro o sea lo
prove it well no No not very proven
demostrará pues no No que muy demostrado
but look at you what people are putting me
pero fíjate tú que me está poniendo la
in the chat Javi and if you because this is very good It's that this is already to have this is already that intelligence is chasing you this what is this is trending topi today or in other words Rocío Carrasco convicted for not paying child support finds her children in court and stops
hijos en el juzgado y le retira el
greeting them and the smartest of the Rosa tide
saludo y los más listos de la marea Rosa
make trends hashtag to
hacen tendencias hashtag a de
abuser I mean this is already
maltratador O sea que esto ya es la
intelligence runs after you
inteligencia sale corriendo detrás tuya
but it's that  you run A lot it's that you
pero es que tú corres Mucho es que tú
run a lot and it doesn't reach you
corres mucho y no te llega a alcanzar
okay And look at the messages that they have
vale Y fíjate tú los mensajes que me han
sent me to this tweet okay it's that you are very
puesto a este tweet vale es que eres muy
short Well there is one that Javi sent me
cortito Bueno hay una que me ha puesto
in the chat a while ago and you what would you
en el chat hace un rato Javi y tú qué
do if your children asked you for jail
harías si tus hijos te piden cárcel
man let's see I
hombre a ver
think that what I would do would be pay the
creo que lo que yo haría sería pagar la
child support that corresponds to me Then maybe
pensión que me corresponda Entonces a lo
there they would not ask you for jail okay I think
mejor ahí ya no te pedirían cárcel vale
that there I think we would start
Yo creo que ahí yo creo que partiríamos
from that base very short the judge
desde esa base muy cortito la jueza
applies the minimum sentence for something it's for something that's what I was
aplica la pena mínima por algo es por
wondering
algo es eso es lo que me preguntaba
before I say it will be because of the mitigating circumstance that
antes digo será por el atenuante de que
the son took
el hijo le haya quitado
these Sources is telling you that he has
antes estas Fuentes te está diciendo que
given the minimum sentence Because well
la ha puesto la pena mínima Porque bueno
because it is still very bad So you have
porque todavía es muy malo Entonces has
committed a little bit of a crime but I am
cometido un poquito un delito pero te
going to sentence you to the minimum because
voy a condenar a lo mínimo porque
Antonio is very bad he wants
Antonio es muy malo quiere que figuren
the sentence to be included that the boy does not have the
la sentencia que el chico no tiene
capacity to discern Who filed the
capacidad para discernir Quién puso la
complaint who does the son against the
denuncia quién pone el hijo contra la
mother who manipulates him that is
madre quién lo manipula eso es violencia
vicarious violence let's see if you understand Okay I mean if it
vicaria a ver si te entera Ya O sea si
's you how is it that we can't go back
eres tú cómo es que no podemos volver a
this please I mean the level They
esto por favor O sea el nivel Es que la
condemn her and it is vicarious violence
condenan a ella y es violencia vicaria
This is already to pull your
Es que esto ya es para tirarse de los
hair out and I'm not telling you that they are those with the
pelos y no te digo que sean de los de la
marine head
cabeza marina
Me neither Then we would have to
Yo tampoco Entonces nos tendríamos que
pull our hair out we have no
tirar de los pelos de la cabeza no nos
other choice Marina you are very pretty and you
queda otra Marina eres muy guapa y le
add the tasty old man of the king of
sumas al viejo sabroso del rey del
gossip a kiss to both of you Javi look at your
salseo un beso a los dos Javi mira tu
Instagram they will like it
Instagram les gustará
yes look at it maybe he
sí míralo que a lo mejor es que nos ha
sent us a chocolate cake they will like it
mandado una tarta de chocolate les
Maybe as urgent no Hey it
gustará A lo mejor como urgente no Oye
seems a little heavy to me this is a little the
me parece un poco heavy esto es un poco
way to rebel not theirs there is no
la forma de rebelarse no de ellas no hay
other argument there is nothing to say
otro argumento no hay nada que decir
against this sentence against this
contra esta sentencia contra esta
reality
realidad
in the face of this you cannot do you cannot
ante esto no puedes hacer no puedes
do anything but I just don't understand
hacer nada pero es que no entiendo
besides they continue because the subject is over And
además siguen porque el tema Ya está Y
although the subject is banned And although the
aunque el tema esté vetado Y aunque el
subject is still there the fight continues my goodness my
tema esté se sigue sigue la lucha madre
goodness on top of that trending topi But
mía madre mía encima trending topi Pero
how I want you to go eat your
qué ganitas de que tengas que ir a comer
[ __ ] in jail you piece of idiot
el rabo a la cárcel pedazo de imbécil
that To whom you yes yes yes yes yes like
eso A quién a ti sí sí sí sí sí como que
I have to go in and  they're going to put him in
yo tengo que entrar y lo van a meter la
jail I'm going to have to go suck
cárcel yo voy a tener que ir a chuparle
his [ __ ] later My God Javi for God's sake
la [__] luego Dios mío Javi por Dios
cynical and a bad person is what you are
cínico y mala persona es lo que eres
but let's see he's lost It's that they
pero a ver está perdido Es que la han
convicted her So I'm not
condenado O sea que yo no la estoy
enjoying it
disfrutando
my tweet is Rocío Carrasco convicted for
mi tweet es Rocío Carrasco condenada por
not paying child support she
no pagar la pensión de su hijo se
meets her children in court and
encuentra con sus hijos en el juzgado y
stops greeting them the geniuses of the
le retira el saludo los genios de la
Rosa two point tide hashtag trends
marea Rosa dos puntos hashtag tendencias
Antonia vi abuser but it's just that I don't
Antonia vi maltratador pero es que no A
see there's nothing in those
ver es que no hay ahí nada en esas
heads I mean I ca
cabezas
n't do anything here anymore I
o sea yo aquí ya no puedo hacer nada yo
'm putting it to you But look Javi if it had
os estoy poniéndola Pero mira Javi si
been the other way around if it had been
hubiera sido al revés si hubiera sido
something the other way around here the difference is
algo al revés aquí la diferencia se
Commented And if there is something if they had
Comenta Y si hay algo si hubieran
convicted Antonio David for something else it is
condenado Antonio David por otra se
Commented in the most
Comenta de una manera de la forma más
objective way possible or we give our opinions
objetiva posible o se hacen opinamos
but it's that I do
pero es que estas barbaridades
n't understand these atrocities clearly I don't wish I don't
no entiendo claro Yo no le deseo
wish Antonio vi to be convicted
no le deseo Antonio vi que le condenen
but it's not only Ruso
pero es que tampoco solo deseaba ruso
Carrasco that wished what I wish is that an
Carrasco yo lo que deseo que llegue a un
agreement is reached and everyone is left alone and
acuerdo y se dejen todos en paz y